<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">lab1_2</string>
    <string name="back_btn">Back</string>
    <string name="main_name">Cooking recipes</string>
    <string name="brk_name">Breakfast</string>
    <string name="lnch_name">Lunch</string>
    <string name="dnn_name">Dinner</string>
    <string name="lng_name">Language selection</string>
    <string name="lng_btn">Russian</string>
    <string name="lng_btn2">English</string>
    <string name="lng_btn3">Japanese</string>
    <string name="brk_1">Omelette</string>
    <string name="ingr">Ingredients:</string>
    <string name="brk_1_2">1. Eggs\n2. Milk\n3. Ghee\n4. Salt</string>
    <string name="prig">Preparation:</string>
    <string name="brk_1_3">1. Wash the eggs well. Carefully break them into a bowl.\n2. Mix the eggs with a fork or whisk.\n3. Lightly salt the omelette mixture.\n4. Pour milk into the egg mixture.\n5. Stir the omelette mixture until smooth.\n6. Grease the pan in which you will cook the omelette with oil. Heat a frying pan with oil well.\n7. Pour the omelette mixture into the pan. Cook on low heat. The omelet will be ready when there are no liquid areas left in the entire egg mass.</string>
    <string name="brk_2">Oatmeal</string>
    <string name="brk_2_2">1. Oatmeal\n2. Milk\n3. Butter\n4. Sugar\n5. Salt</string>
    <string name="brk_2_3">1. Take a suitable saucepan for cooking porridge. Add cereal, pour milk. Add salt and sugar.\n2. Place the saucepan with the porridge on medium heat.\n3. Meanwhile, the milk will boil, stir it so that the flakes do not stick to the bottom.\n4. Leave the porridge to cook over low heat for 15-20 minutes.\n5. When the porridge is ready, turn off the heat and add butter.</string>
    <string name="brk_3">Cottage cheese casserole</string>
    <string name="brk_3_2">1. Cottage cheese\n2. Semolina\n3. Sugar\n4. Butter\n5. Milk\n6. Eggs\n7. Vanillin</string>
    <string name="brk_3_3">1. Rub the cottage cheese through a fine sieve or punch it with a blender.\n2. In a suitable size container, combine eggs with sugar. Beat the mixture with a mixer until a stable fluffy foam forms. Add grated cottage cheese and milk. Continue beating until smooth.\n3. Add soft butter. Beat the mixture again until smooth.\n4. Add semolina gradually. Each time, beat the mixture with a mixer at low speed.\n5. Leave the dough for 15-30 minutes for the cereal to swell. In advance, 10-20 minutes before baking, turn on the oven to preheat to 180°C. Transfer the dough to a suitable baking dish.\n6. Bake the casserole for about 30 minutes until golden brown. Cool the finished casserole.</string>
    <string name="lnch_1">Pork stew</string>
    <string name="lnch_1_2">1. Pork\n2. Potato\n3. Broth\n4. Bell pepper\n5. Bow\n6. Carrot\n7. Vegetable oil\n8. Ground black pepper\n9. Salt</string>
    <string name="lnch_1_3">1. Wash the pork and cut into medium pieces.\n2. Peel the potatoes. Cut the tubers.\n3. Cut a medium or large sized onion into four pieces.\n4. Cut the carrots into not very thin slices.\n5. Peel the bell pepper from seeds and stems and cut into medium pieces.\n6. Heat some vegetable oil in a frying pan. Fry the pork on it until golden brown. At the end, salt and pepper the meat.\n7. Combine all the vegetables in a bowl, pour in the remaining vegetable oil. Salt, pepper and mix everything.\n8. Transfer meat and vegetables to a baking dish. Pour in the broth.\n9. Cover the pan with foil or a heat-resistant lid, if you have one, and place in an oven preheated to 180°C. Baking time 1-1.5 hours.\n10. Sprinkle the finished roast with chopped herbs.</string>
    <string name="lnch_2">Chicken soup</string>
    <string name="lnch_2_2">1. Chicken\n2. Potato\n3. Onions\n4. Carrot\n5. Bell pepper\n6. Water\n7. Vegetable oil\n8. Salt\n9. Dry spices</string>
    <string name="lnch_2_3">1. Rinse the chicken, place it in a saucepan and cover with water. Place on the fire and bring to a boil. Cook over low heat for 25-30 minutes. Salt it a little. When the chicken is cooked, remove it from the broth, cool slightly and separate the meat from the bones. Strain the broth. Return the meat to the broth and return to the heat. Bring to a boil.\n2. Cut the peeled potatoes into small pieces and place in the boiling broth. Boil the potatoes for 15-20 minutes. During cooking, the potatoes will become soft.\n3. While the potatoes are cooking, start frying the vegetables. Peel the onions and carrots and rinse. Finely chop the onion and grate the carrots on a coarse grater. Pour a little vegetable oil into a frying pan and fry the vegetables over low heat for a couple of minutes. Then add the chopped bell pepper to the pan. Peppers can be cut into large or small pieces. Fry all the vegetables for another 2-3 minutes and place the fry in the pan with the soup.\n4. Add some salt and spices to the soup. Boil everything together for 1-2 minutes and remove the pan from the heat.</string>
    <string name="lnch_3">Pasta Carbonara</string>
    <string name="lnch_3_2">1. Spaghetti\n2. Bacon\n3. Salt\n4. Water\n5. Olive oil\n6. Cream\n7. Egg yolks\n8. Herbal mixture\n9. Ground black pepper</string>
    <string name="lnch_3_3">1. Pour water into a saucepan of suitable volume, place on the stove and bring to a boil. Add salt. Dip the spaghetti into the water. Cook the pasta in boiling water for 6-8 minutes.\n2. Drain the water through a colander, drizzle the pasta with olive oil and stir.\n3. Prepare the ingredients for the sauce. Cut the bacon slices into square pieces. Heat the oil in a frying pan and fry the bacon until golden brown over medium heat, stirring everything with a spatula.\n4. Pour cream into the pan and stir. Simmer everything, stirring, for one minute.\n5. Add Italian herbs, ground pepper and salt to the sauce. Add the pasta to the pan and stir gently. Keep the dish on the fire for about one minute so that everything warms up well. Remove the pan from the stove.\n6. Add the raw yolk to the carbonara pasta and stir quickly so that the yolk spreads throughout the dish.</string>
    <string name="dnn_1">Buckwheat according to merchant</string>
    <string name="dnn_1_2">1. Buckwheat\n2. Chicken\n3. Bow\n4. Carrot\n5. Tomato paste\n6. Water\n7. Vegetable oil\n8. Dry spices\n9. Salt</string>
    <string name="dnn_1_3">1. Peel the onions and carrots and rinse in water. Sort the buckwheat, removing debris and unrefined grains. Rinse it several times in cold water.\n2. Wash the chicken meat and dry it well. Cut it into small pieces. Pour a little vegetable oil into a hot frying pan and place pieces of chopped chicken meat. Fry it over high heat for 7-10 minutes until it browns a little.\n3. While the chicken is frying, chop the onion and grate the carrots on a coarse grater.\n4. Then add the onions and carrots to the pan with the meat. Stir and fry everything together for another 3-4 minutes.\n5. Place the washed buckwheat in the pan. Boil the water. Stir the tomato paste in hot water and pour it over the buckwheat. Add a little salt and spices to taste. Stir and bring to a boil. Cover the pan with a lid and cook over low heat for 13-15 minutes.\n6. During stewing, buckwheat will absorb water. Taste the buckwheat. It should be soft.</string>
    <string name="dnn_2">Lasagna</string>
    <string name="dnn_2_2">1. Minced meat\n2. Tomatoes\n3. Bow\n4. Lasagna sheets\n5. Garlic\n6. Tomato paste\n7. Hard cheese\n8. Vegetable oil\n9. Salt</string>
    <string name="dnn_2_3">1. Peel the onion and cut into arbitrarily small pieces.\n2. Heat the vegetable oil in a frying pan and fry the minced meat and onion in it for five minutes, stirring constantly.\n3. Peel the garlic and chop finely. Wash the tomatoes and cut into cubes. You can first remove the skin from the tomato. Add tomato paste, chopped tomatoes and garlic to the frying pan with the minced meat and onions. Add salt to taste.\n4. Mix everything well, reduce the heat to medium and simmer the minced meat under a closed lid for about 10 minutes. At this stage, you can add a pinch of basil to the minced meat.\n5. While the minced meat is stewing, prepare the Bechamel sauce. To do this, melt the butter in a saucepan over low heat.\n6. Add flour and, stirring continuously with a whisk, lightly fry it in melted butter.\n7. Gradually pour in the milk, continuing to stir the mixture with a whisk so that no lumps form. Bring the mixture to the consistency of thick cream, remove from heat and cool.\n8. Grease the bottom of the baking dish with vegetable oil or line it with baking paper. Fill the bottom with Bechamel sauce.\n9. Lay out the lasagna sheets as the first layer. Pour the sauce over the top of the sheets again.\n10. Place the next layer of minced meat and sprinkle it with lightly grated cheese.\n11. Pour the sauce over the minced meat. Continue adding layers until the mold is filled. The last layer with sheets must be filled with sauce very well, especially the edges, otherwise there is a chance that the sheet of dough will dry out and burn during the cooking process.\n12. Sprinkle the final layer with grated cheese.\n13. Place the lasagna in an oven preheated to 190-200 degrees for 30-35 minutes. Focus on the fact that the lasagna should form an appetizing golden crust. Remove the finished dish from the oven and let it sit for about 10 minutes.</string>
    <string name="dnn_3">Caesar salad</string>
    <string name="dnn_3_2">1. Iceberg salad\n2. Chicken fillet\n3. Cherry tomatoes\n4. Loaf\n5. Parmesan\n6. Garlic\n7. Vegetable oil\n8. Salt\n9. Ground black pepper\n10. Olive oil\n11. Parmesan\n12. Eggs\n13. Mustard\n14. Sugar</string>
    <string name="dnn_3_3">1. Cut the loaf into small cubes.\n2. Pour a little vegetable oil into the frying pan, add a peeled and crushed clove of garlic. Add sliced bread and stir. Fry the croutons over low heat until crispy. They need to be stirred from time to time.\n3. Cut the chicken fillet into small medallions of the same size. Salt and pepper them.\n4. Fry the fillet in a frying pan with a small amount of vegetable oil on both sides until golden brown. Remove the finished fillet from the pan and cool.\n5. Prepare ingredients for making sauce. Place the egg in a glass and pour boiling water over it. Keep it like this for a minute or two.\n6. Break the prepared egg into a mixing glass, add Parmesan, mustard, sugar, salt, butter and chopped garlic.\n7. Using short pulse movements, whisk all ingredients until it forms a sauce.\n8. Cut the cooled fillet into small pieces.\n9. Tear the lettuce leaves into the bottom of the plate. Pour the sauce over the salad.\n10. Arrange the chicken pieces and chopped tomatoes.\n11. Place crackers on top. Sprinkle with grated Parmesan.\n12. Finally, pour the sauce over the entire salad again.</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel timer</string>
    <string name="n1">Timer item №1</string>
    <string name="n2">Timer item №2</string>
    <string name="n3">Timer item №3</string>
    <string name="n4">Timer item №4</string>
    <string name="n5_1">Timer item 5-1</string>
    <string name="n5_2">Timer item 5-2</string>
    <string name="n6">Timer item №6</string>
    <string name="n7">Timer item №7</string>
    <string name="n9">Timer item №9</string>
    <string name="n5">Timer item №5</string>
    <string name="n13_1">Timer item 13-1</string>
    <string name="n13_2">Timer item 13-2</string>
    <string name="brk_voice">Recipe voiceover</string>
</resources>